Father.
You need to get as far away as possible.
Why must I run away?
Why? Why should I be afraid?
Its power is overwhelming.
You can't win against it.
It's coming.
Who, Father? Who's coming? Who?
Still here, Lieutenant?
In a while, Sarge.
- I'm heading out first.
- Yes.
(Khmer language)
What do you want?
Why did you do that?
We have a lot to talk about.
Arnon, right?
It's possible to wonder why
I'm here and what to do.
Am I here to kill.
The answer is no.
Don't be afraid.
First, let me introduce myself.
My name is
God.
G- O- D.
Which means.
God.
Or as some might call me the Creator..
Deity.
- The Almighty.
- I don't want to know.
Hey, shh... I’m not finished.
A being of divine and miraculous power.
With powers so great that...
People revere and worship.
Worship?
This is getting ridiculous.
- This.
- Umm.
Hey!
What did you do to my boss, huh?
Are you into black magic?
I need you to find someone.
Because I know you're the one.
Who runs this city, aren't you?
Hah!
If you're so great, why not find them yourself?
I'm just biding my time.
So what?
You want me to be your lackey? Is that it?
What gives you the right?
I’m making you my partner.
Partner.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not going to do anything.
I've killed enough people today.
What the hell do you want me to do?
You'll see.
Put your hands together and receive the blessing.
Happy Birthday. Happy.
Stay safe.
Stay strong.
And be a good man, just like your father.
Yes, Mom.
I wish your father were here with us.
I believe he's still watching over us.
I want to believe that too, Mom.
That he’s out there, protecting us.
Umm.
- Thank you, Mom.
- Umm.
That's touching.
What the hell is so touching?
You little bitch.
Oh man, want to be just like them.
Aw, man!
Ever since I was born,
I’ve never felt an ounce of warmth from my mother.
Yeah.
- Never had a mom. So what...
you wanna be one for me? Huh?
- Come, come and hug Mommy.
- Okay, sure. Hey!
- Oh no, I don't want to get diarrhea.
- Get away from me, kid!
Oh, diarrhea?
Hey, Tun.
How was it? Was it okay?
Good, good, it works.
Damn, you guy's idea is fucking brilliant.
See? It’s just the three of us.
We’re not stealing each other’s customers.
No stealing, it’s a completely different groups.
Hell, even I want to start
a business like this myself.
If you guys open this place,
I’m basically gonna live at this shop.
Do it.
That's a good thing.
Because if you're going to come here.
I’m gonna go to your place instead.
I heard the Japanese girls at your spot are hot.
- Damn, we even have Russians too.
- Haha! Oh, I've always had a thing for Westerners.
You never change, Joe. Still a total asshole.
God, you guys are unbelievable.
Hey, after this bottle, I’m heading out.
Aren't you gonna stay and watch us fight?
Shit, the shop just texted me.
The place is getting packed.
Oh.
Yeah, drive safe. If we
close up early, I might join you at your shop.
- Come on over. You’re always welcome.
- I'm in.
- Bring the whole gang. It’s my treat today.
- You got it.
- Hell yeah, buddy.
- Damn, what a baller.
Okay.
- I'm out. See ya, see ya!
- Ok.
- Bye Bye.
- Bye.
- See you.
- See ya. I'll be right behind you.
- drive safe.
- Thanks.
Be careful.
- Yeah.
- Watch your step.
- Ow! Your head!
- Ow!
Aha! You tripped!
- You watch too much comedy.
- Yeah.
I can see it, the future looks good.
Visualize this with me.
The counter goes right in the middle,
and we’ll have a DJ over there on the right.
I'll turn that into the kitchen.
- And you, Foon
- Yeah.
You better help out in the shop too.
Washing dishes, serving food,
clearing tables, and arranging chairs.
You’re basically making me your servant.
Don't call it that. Call yourself the Chief of Servant.
Is the rent expensive?
It's Phu- Yai Tia’s place. My mom knows him,
so he'll give us a cheap rate.
No problem there.
The only problem is the damn police.
They’re going to be come for a cut.
These Scumbags never freaking disappear, do they?
Doesn't matter if we're legit.
these bastards.
Always find a way to extort us.
Damn, now I'm all stressed out.
End.
Don't worry about it.
Just pay them off and get it over with.
It’ll make things easier for you.
So, this place.
When are you going to start?
Pretty soon.
- Then we're definitely going to have some fun.
- Fun, my ass!
- Why?
- It's gonna be exhausting.
You'll just end up dumping all the work on me.
If not you, then who? You think I'll get tips
if I serve? the guys here aren't looking for me.
Alright, enough. Hey!
Alright, I'm heading out.
I'm heading over to Tun's place.
You wanna come with? I can give you a ride.
- I'm done for today.
- No.
Alright then. I'll head out now.
Goodluck, man.
Alright you shits, get home safe.
- Umm.
- Umm. Don't worry.
With Foon around, the dogs won't dare to bite.
I’ll bite you myself.
- Whoops! I’m vaccinated!
- I'm biting your head off first!
- Let's get everything cleared together.
- Oh, shit!
What did Singha drop? Wait, is this a shell.
Let me see.
Is it?
Hey, it's not a shell.
This is a 'Bia Gae'.
A Bia Gae?
Yeah, his thing protects
you from curses and bad energy.
What the hell.
Keep it for Singha.
Yo, Tun.
Hey, Singha. Cancel for now.
I'm almost there! What the fuck, man?
I'm heading to the police station.
Some Westerner is brawling with a Chinese guy.
That's it.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, shit!
(2309 B.E.)
I heard they have
Sorcerer- warriors.
Protecting Bang Rachan, is that right?
I don't think so.
It might just be a rumor.
To strike fear into our soldiers.
Don't be so careless.
Countless times we have attacked their camp.
Their camp has never fallen.
They must have something
powerful protecting them.
It is far too quiet.
Something is definitely wrong.
Do they already know?
That we are coming?
That’s why they’ve prepared themselves.
Hey.
- Hey.
Kill Them!
You think I don't know?
If you've got tricks, so do I.
A ghost army like yours.
How tough can you really be?
I have my own master of Khmer sorcerer.
So, you're the disciples of Master Thammachote?
There is still one more left.
At Bang Rachan.
Armed with twin axes.
Do you see that light in the distance?
The entire village is up in flames.
It is such a beautiful sight.
The wailing of the villagers.
It sounds absolutely divine.
Without you,
Everything becomes so much easier.
You are a traitor.
You betrayed your own motherland.
I curse you.
This is very strange.
I've never seen a case like this before.
The patient was in a deep sleep,
unable to wake up for six days.
But on the seventh day,
he woke up vomiting blood.
Yet, his vital signs remain perfectly normal.
And he just got up as if
he had woken up from a normal sleep.
It's very bizarre.
Doctor.
Do you think this case
could be related to black magic?
My diagnosis is limited
to the realm of science. Beyond that.
I cannot offer any opinion.
And... how much longer
will he be hospitalized?
He's cleared to go home.
Please excuse me.
There's an urgent case.
Oh.
Whoa, easy there.
Damn.
It’s like you haven't eaten in three days.
Seven days, man!
Seven days!
I’m fucking starving!
So, what was wrong with you exactly?
You don't even look sick.
It’s more like you just changed where you sleep.
God damn it.
I saw this huge guy, like, pitch black.
I almost couldn't swerve in time.
Before I blacked out.
I saw ghosts surrounding me everywhere.
Or maybe you.
Or have you been messing around too much?
- What do you mean?
- You're just hallucinating.
- I’m not seeing things. I’m being serious!
- You're out of your mind. Just keep eating.
- Let's go. Pack your things, we're going home.
- Nonsense.
Auntie, so what's wrong with Singha anyway?
Just go pack your things, Foon. Hurry up!
Other patients are waiting for this bed.
If you stay one more night.
I won't have any money left to pay the medical bills!
Go. Pack up.
Are you full yet?
Not yet, Mom.
We are such pathetic, broke citizens.
(Kongdet : Bring Singha here, ASAP!)
Got any Pad Kaprao?
You're asking for Kaprao in a hospital?
I'll go out and buy it for you.
What kind of Kaprao do you want?
Wow, who would ever believe this?
Seven nights in the hospital,
and he wakes up walking like nothing happened.
Hey, wait for me!
- Hey.
- What are you mumbling about?
Look, walking like a pro.
If you'd been here that day,
you probably wouldn't have crashed
That’s got nothing to do with it. Didn’t you see?
There isn't a scratch on me.
Yeah, sure. I believe you.
And I'm still hungry!
I haven't even finished eating and
I'm already getting kicked out of the hospital.
Alright. I'll buy you that Kaprao.
You're such a nag.
Hey
I'll be right back. You guys keep talking.
- Where to?
- Why?
Hey, check on the shop.
Working.
- Suit yourself, man. Be my guest.
- You bastard!
So busy.
Are you going to check on the shop
and customers, or just go and eat with them?
- Damn you!
- You're a real asshole.
Other shops recommend their menu, but this
asshole just says, Get this one, I like it!
- So busy, man! The place is packed.
- Busy, my ass! There are only six tables.
- Nah, Joe is just...
- Huh?
The doc was stuttering
when I asked him what happened to Singha.
You should've told him Singh is basically The Hulk.
He’s a superhero, a superhuman.
He’s tough.
Because he's been exposed
to so many chemicals.
Geez, so aggressive!
Watch it! I'll have my crew
from the squid boat come over and kick your ass.
- You're such a sadist.
- Yeah, for real.
Squid fishing, you idiot!
What a weird question.
Hey, you guys.
Did you see something over there?
- Where?
- Umm.
- There’s nothing there. Not even a single dog.
- Yeah, nothing.
Are you high on IV fluids or something?
Why don't you go to bed? Or just go home?
- You're freaking losing it.
- Yeah.
- Do you have a concussion or something?
- Then forget it. There's nothing there.
- Oh my god.
- He already said that once back at the hospital.
What the hell is with this wind?
What is it this time, Singha?
Why are you rubbing your eyes so hard?
- Singha.
- Hey.
Your eyes are super red.
- Singha. Singha.
- Hey, Singha.
Easy, Singha.
What's wrong with Singha?
Singha. Can you hear me? Singha.
- Singha.
- I don't know what's wrong with him, Mom.
He’s burning up. Should we head to the hospital?
Foon, Joe! Carry Singha to the car. Quick!
- Okay.
- Hurry up!
- Count with me.
- Coming! Hold on, hold on!
One, two, three... Up! Got him. He’s in. Okay.
- Oh. Damn it.
- One, two, three.
Oh.
- Careful! Go, go. Watch his head!
- Left, left!
- Left. Left.
- Watch his head! Careful.
- Hurry up, you guys! Be careful!
- Auntie.
Quick! Before it's too late!
- Just grabbed Buddha amulets and ignoring your son!
- Get him in the car.
Ugh, Watch his head.
- Singha,
- Singha, come here.
Hang in there, damn it! Where's all your strength gone?
Fuck!
Damn it.
Carrying a fridge for
a friend wasn't even this heavy!
This pair is really looking for trouble lately.
No idea where they're off to this time.
Stay out of it. Worry about yourself.
Guys come help me, quick!
- Quick!
- Yes.
Which way? This way, right?
Come.
Come. Hurry!
Stay strong, brother.
- Come this way. This way, hurry!
- Strong? He's way past being strong.
- Quickly. Quick!
- Stay strong, brother.
- Come. Quickly!
- Watch the stairs!
- Hey! Watch his legs!
My respects, Luang Ta.
You two, hurry up and get Singha inside.
Yes, Luang Ta.
Singha is going to be okay, isn't he?
Go inside first.
Yes.
As for you.
Go back to where you belong.
Don't create more karma here.
Go.
The wandering curse of the wind.
Khmer black magic, carried by the breeze.
Your son, Singh, was born on 9th September.
His father intended to pass down
this dark art through his very bloodline.
But the dark elements
within him overwhelmed the light.
Your husband fell deep
into the abyss of black magic.
Until he was trapped, with no way out.
Let him lie in the enchanted herb bath for now.
I will try my own way.
It’s going to take some time.
But there is no guarantee that
Singha will ever be the same person again.
Sometimes
We can't dictate our own destiny.
Only Karma is the one that decides.
(Praying)
Good, good. That's good.
Hello, Big Boss.
I'm Arnon.
Is there anything I can do for you, sir?
Sia Rambo.
I’ve heard your name,
but this is the first time we've met in person.
Respect, sir.
Respect? Hell no. People are
dying left and right. What's going on?
Are you involved in every single one of these deaths?
And this city. What exactly are you protecting here?
Tell me about it.
I don't know, I'm not involved, and...
Nothing.
- Come on, take a seat first.
- It's alright. I'm just here for business.
It's alright.
Being the provincial governor
doesn't mean you can just do whatever you want.
In this town, you know
there are many layers of powerful people.
You're trash.
I thought my brother, Akkapol
would run this city forever, but now he’s gone.
If that’s all, I’ll be taking my leave now.
Wait! You now I have a huge family.
I can't look after everyone.
Look at this my drug shipment just got ripped off.
My own nephew, Chon, tipped off
the Narcotics Board to bust me and my stash.
And you. You're working
for Senator Namchai, aren't you?
You think I don't know?
You piece of shit!
You think you can take over this city? You an idiot!
Get out!
(Take care of it.)
Chicken.
You bastard.
Sia! Sia, what's wrong?
Sia.
Security! Help!
Fuck.
This city is so beautiful at night.
But I suppose it’s worth the effort of...
Kneeling and begging for mercy,
Pleading.
Only to betray them in cold blood.
Well...
Quite worth it, indeed.
With you by my side,
Everything just seems so easy.
But it costs a fortune.
Okay.
The person I’ve been looking for is getting close.
Who? This person you're searching for?
The one I have some unfinished business with.
Bitch!
Where the hell are you going?
What are you doing?
Stay out of this!
You demon!
You think you can take my life?
Never.
You’re not getting my life!
We have three bodies at the scene.
The middle- aged male is a former
Member of Parliament for the Phumtham Party.
His name is Mr. Weerawat Nalodom.
The middle- aged female is identified as his wife.
And the teenage victim.
Is their son.
No, that’s not right.
There’s a girl in the bedroom.
Inspector.
This doesn't look like a normal incident anymore.
The patterns of death are highly
unusual across the board.
And every victim is tied to politics and bribery.
What kind of city is this?
There are hardly any reporters.
It’s like people die
and then just vanish into thin air.
No news, no leads,
no evidence linking anything together.
Witnesses are kept silent by fear.
Talk and end up dead.
What a civilized country we live in.
Lieutenant.
Look at this.
They’ve decoded the security footage.
You bastard.
You're coming for my life?
And all that.
It’s just like every other case we’ve had.
There was no trace of the killer.
No hired gun.
Every case looks like a suicide.
Or just an accident.
It looks like an overdose.
Or a severe mental breakdown.
Or if there’s a real connection here.
It has to be related to this.
The drugs?
And how does that link to homicide cases?
All the evidence in our hands.
Shows a connection to this
specific drug at every crime scene.
It must come from the same source.
I’ll do my best to trace it back to the source.
(Praying)
Thank you very much, Mr. Arnon.
For providing scholarships
to these underprivileged children.
It’s my pleasure.
Then, I’d like to take a picture for the records.
Yes, sure.
Children, please form a line.
Ohm... thump- thump, thump- thump.
Heavy stone, solid within.
My skull is forged in steel
Against diamond blades,
spears, wooden arrows, and firelocks.
By the power of merit, magic,
and the essence of a hundred and eight roots.
Descend and dwell within my body.
(Chanting)
From now on.
You shall be invulnerable.
No blade can cut you, no bullet can pierce you.
Singha, damn it! What's the plan?
They betrayed each other.
They're coming for the drugs.
And they're everywhere outside!
Shit!
Singha, I’m scared.
Follow my lead.
- Hey.
- Shit, Singha.
We're fucked!
Those bastards! Goddamn!
Bastards!
Joe.
Come on.
Singha.
I'm sure the cops are gonna come after us.
Just act normal, Joe.
I’m telling you, those dealers
are definitely gonna come and kill us.
And then there’s home.
The cops might not know, but I bet they do.
They’re definitely coming to finish us off.
Go home now and don't make a sound.
- Go.
- How about you?
Leave! I told you to leave! Go!
Woah, chill the fuck out, man!
Why you jonesing so hard?
Give me the money.
I'll call you.
- Hey, what are you up to?
- Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Selling drugs.
You’re dealing drugs right outside the precinct?
Go.
Hey, I told you to go! Just walk!
Singha's been busted, man.
What's Next?
Have you eaten yet?
Yes, I have.
You'll be out soon.
I left some things for you with the guard.
Luckily, business is slow
because of the long weekend.
I made a big bag of Kaphrao
with bamboo shoots for you.
Share it with the other guys inside, okay?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
- Mom.
- I’m heading out now, Officer.
I brought some snacks for you as well, Officer.
Please take care of my son.
It’s karma.
It depends on how he uses that karma.
Whether for good or for evil.
His destiny is quite more special than others.
It's unlikely to be karma
trailing him from a past life.
It’s bound to these dens of vice.
I don't want him to end up like his father.
Who can escape their fate?
Just look at me.
I should never have gotten into this life.
It haunts you, forced to live in the shadows.
(Praying)
Singha.
Singha, Son.
Can you hear me? Singha.
What happened? What's wrong with me?
Singha.
After tonight, you'll never be the same again.
Your fate has reached its end.
Someone is looking to take your soul for a ritual.
A man without a soul.
You know what that means?
Are you insane?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
I'll tell you about it later.
They’re starting to find out that I’m back.
About what I saw that day.
When they shot you.
What was that?
Were you wearing a vest?
Or are you actually bulletproof?
You have to learn that for yourself, Singha.
I need to get moving.
If I stay any longer, they'll definitely find me.
Mom.
Singha.
There’s so much you haven't told me, Mom.
Another one of those sorcerers has arrived?